Music
Please subscribe to our channel!
Everyone.
We would like to do a Christmas only gift exchange!
Yay!
The more you have, the less trouble you'll have.
No doubt about it.
I'm sure of it.
You know what?
I need you to melt it down.
Music is important, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah? - Yeah.
It instantly relaxes you.
You can sit and watch it like a normal person.
I can consume it.
Oh, on the contrary?
Yes, the opposite.
I like to feel embarrassed.
Seriously?
Don't even get me started on the homemade stuff.
I've been working hard all night.
I'll do my best!
Seriously?
We'll pick the winner in a game of rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
I'm going to get in front of the camera.
I'll tell them what's in mine.
Wow!
I'd like to repeat the process.
And so on and so forth.
Yes, sir.
You know, I've got a rule.
I'd like to make one rule.
If Ryota gets homemade Ryota
Can I ask him to do it alone as usual?
No, no, that's impossible.
Then...
Then what would you do?
Well, for example, if I pull mine.
I mean, I'd like to trade mine.
And if you come forward, we'll trade you that, too.
Yes, sure.
Then we'll have a happy Christmas.
Amicable.
At any rate, those people, too.
We'll put it in everyone's hands for now.
Don't say anything until it's in your hands.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's do it!
First, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Go, go, show!
Show! Show!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Two, two, two, two.
Wow.
Whoa.
You.
First, goo rock-paper-scissors!
Shoo!
Ah, easy
But, but, but...
I'll be on camera.
But, no, but honestly
I don't care what everyone's present is.
Anything.
Sweet siren.
I'm really...
I'm so happy to see so many presents!
I don't know what to pick!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
I want to keep it warm until now!
And this... it's too much to lift up!
You're right, if you lift it up, it's too much!
Don't touch it!
I won't hold it.
Don't hold it, don't hold it.
Oh, my eyes. My eyes.
I'll touch you.
With your eyes. With your eyes.
Here!
Oh! Oh!
Come on. Come on.
Does that mean I can open it?
I wonder what's in the bag.
What?
Oh, I can look?
Yeah.
Shhh!
Come on.
Why?
All he said was "shhh.
Oh!
What?
Speaker!
Oh!
You said you were happy.
I'm so happy!
Oh, this might make the bathroom even louder.
You read that.
I'm glad you said something.
I was just trying to keep everyone out of the neighborhood.
Uh, yeah.
Neighborhood nuisance.
Glad!
Stylish.
I don't have any eye circles.
It's cool, right?
Okay, I want to hold it like this.
Okay, let's do three poses in front of the camera.
Uh... What?
One, two, three.
Oh!
Okay!
Oh, great.
I'm so happy.
You did it.
Yes!
Okay, you can go on now.
Yes, sir.
Masaya.
Masaya, Masaya.
I like you.
Masaya, think about it.
I like polka dots.
Masaya, can I say polka dots?
You can say polka dots.
Polka dots are good, right?
No, polka dots are totally fine.
They're very attractive.
But I'm interested in the tiny ones.
Here it is.
I have tiny ones right here.
Oh!
But...
I wonder what this is.
No, but maybe there was a clue in our earlier discussion.
What's this?
It's very classy, isn't it?
Yeah, but I love luxury.
Oh, oh, here we go.
It's nice.
And here it is.
Oh!
It's nice.
It sure has a luxurious feel to it.
It sure is.
And there's only one.
What do you mean?
No, I don't know yet.
You don't know yet.
No, wow.
I don't know either.
But...
Oh, the transfer.
But it doesn't make any noise, does it?
No, it doesn't make any noise.
What do you mean?
You ready? Ready?
Here we go.
Okay.
What?
Huh?
It's Karaboko.
Oh, okay.
Karaboko.
Congratulations, Masaya.
Okay, let's take a look.
First, I'll make it.
Okay, go ahead.
I'm off!
Karaboko!
I see. It's a handwriting.
I see.
I'm going to make one.
The design of this box.
I thought it was a little ahead of its time.
I know, I know, I know.
That's why once a year
I have to be sad.
No, no, no.
Because last year, it was him.
This time, it's Masaya.
That's fine.
Next year, three years, four years from now...
It's already going to be us.
Three years, four years, I don't want it to go on.
I don't care.
I don't care anymore. I don't care anymore.
I don't care anymore.
No worries.
I think that's pretty good, don't you?
I tried to keep it simple this time.
By making the photo frame transparent and simple
I thought the design would stand out by making the photo frame transparent and simple.
Fasten the clasp and you're done!
I'm glad you like it.
I did it because I worked hard on it.
It's better than I thought it would be.
This is what it's going to look like when I give it out at home
I mean, this is what it's going to look like when I put it up.
And now it's finished.
Heart.
Here it is.
Wow!
It's so long!
Sorry, it's so complicated.
The important part of the design this time was, as always, simplicity.
Simple!
Simple, simple, simple.
Simple and easy to use
I think it's easy to use.
I'll hang it up if you like.
I think it would be a good idea to put it on my desk or something.
I'll put it on my desk or something.
Well, I hope you guys take good care of it.
Happy MediChristmas!
Ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wow! Wow!
No, but it's fashionable now.
Stop it!
Christmas!
Oh, my God!
What's this?
Oh, my God! It's some kind of cat sticker I found at home.
Oh, my.
Cut and paste. Thank you.
I don't get it. You were making these.
I know, I know! Congratulations!
It's better than I thought it'd be. Better than I thought it'd be.
And you want to look at the pictures.
And you want to carry it with you.
You want to carry them around with you... and you want to put them in your cell phone.
You're all set.
I'd love to see your pictures. - I'd love to see your pictures.
Well, if you see a picture like that...
Oh, my God!
Oh, that's right.
You know, last time I went, it was my first time.
It was my second time, so I'm a little...
The level has gone up.
The graffiti level has gone up.
It was more painful that time.
That's true.
It's funny that you went out in the middle of the transparency.
Yes, yes.
I wonder if it's like Horonobe.
Already.
Let's fumigate it.
That was fast.
Congratulations!
Happy, happy, happy!
Well, Christmas is good.
Well, that's good.
I'm sure your partner got it.
I'm sure of it. - I'm sure of it.
Well, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
The memories will live on.
Don't get it stuck in the book.
Yes, sir.
Congratulations, congratulations, congratulations.
Meri Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas
Well, so we'll see you again.
The five of us who don't have a set time
Let's play rock-paper-scissors-paper.
All right, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Show
Show.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Aaah!
I knew it was a goo rock-paper-scissors fight at the beginning
Oh, no.
I knew it
Happiness
Victory happiness.
Wow, what's that?
This is made up of slightly different possibilities.
This is a possibility.
It's a possibility.
Just, just wait and see.
Alone.
This is the most fun.
It's fun.
A little bit then
I kinda like this one.
Christmas colors
Definitely.
Easy to pick out.
Oh, I'm pimping it out.
I'm definitely interested.
May I?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't mind.
It's pretty heavy.
I'm pretty seriously concerned.
It's heavy.
What?
Does that remind you?
It's okay.
What? What?
Okay, well, whoever gave you this...
Thank you.
All right.
Merry Christmas.
Wow.
Well...
what, what, what, what
me, me, me
Oh, me.
Hmm?
First year? Uh, what? Already, huh? Well, what's that?
Cash, cash? No, no, no, no, no.
I'm afraid I can't show you.
What? What? Cash?
What? No way!
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Thank you!
I was just wondering what you guys were sending.
Wait for this.
What?
Huh!
Huh!? Whoa!
Whoa! Here it comes!
That's so scary, isn't it? That's amazing!
And you said it! That's it!
What? The one with the noise gate? Amazing, isn't it?
I chose it because it's red.
You really did, didn't you?
You didn't get involved in the question at all.
No, this is the one I use at home.
Oh, really? Really? It's probably the same brand.
Really? Second one.
Oh, my God! Like a different color.
I'm so happy!
I've been wanting one of these for a while. It's so stylish! Yay!
Wow! Wow!
That's good! That's great!
I'm so happy!
Wow, I'll be able to work a little harder now. Thank you.
It's so stylish!
It's so stylish, like it's loaded with noise.
Oh, in that case...
This is...
Oh, this is Noi. Sorry.
I'm glad you're doing so well.
I'm glad you're here.
Nice, nice, nice, you pulled a good one...
I got a good one. Thank you. Hey.
I want you to sign it or something.
That's good, isn't it? No, maybe an autograph.
Why don't you want it? Why not?
Why not? It's worth more.
No, no, no. It's over budget.
Then we're done with both. We're done with both.
Thank you. Thank you.
Here you go.
I'm glad. What do you want to pull?
But, you know, there's still some left.
It's all good. Yeah, all of it.
Everything was good this time. Huh?
It's okay. What's left? What's that?
Eye mask, eye mask, phone stand.
Oh, a piggyback. A piggyback.
There's a chance I could get one of those.
Oh, my God.
No, I mean, this blue one, how much of it is...
Sure, sure, sure. No, no, no, no.
And the comb? That's a giant comb.
And the giant comb? I'd be in a bit of trouble with that comb.
Yeah, sure.
Oh!
You already touched it.
He said it's kind of nice.
I think I'm right.
Wait a minute.
This is amazing.
You're holding it right now, right?
It's heavy.
I'll leave it alone.
No, it's not!
I don't know.
No, I don't.
There's about a hundred of them.
Then let's give them to him.
Here we go.
I got it.
I don't get it.
Oh, no.
Yay.
No, I got it.
It's a hot eye mask, too.
Kousaku picked this out, didn't he?
Mr. Kousaku picked this out, didn't he?
Assorted hot eye masks
Total hot eye masks.
Please, come sit next to me.
Okay?
I chose the hot eye masks.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
And, uh, I have exactly 15 total.
Oh.
Yeah, well, I'm tired.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
You've worked so hard this year just to win.
I'm glad you won the most.
You're right. We don't have any hot eye masks.
About 200 boxes.
They were so cheap.
Not 200 masks.
200 boxes.
I don't need that.
You're right. I don't need it.
But when I got it, I thought...
They're consumables.
It's definitely going to waste.
That's right, and it's because I love you.
So do this.
When I sleep... with Kousaku...
I have a dream.
What about my dream?
What about your dream?
Why not?
I missed you in my dream, didn't I?
I missed you in my dreams, too.
Comfort me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Then I'll see you in my dreams.
He's happy.
I'm glad you're happy.
Thank you very much.
I don't know, you didn't mention it, but...
But the color of this wrapping... it really bothers me.
I touched it.
I'll go with this one.
Oh, it's very impressive.
I think I can see the hole in the base.
We don't have incense that big.
That's for sure.
A little more
But it weighs so much it's hard to believe it's incense.
That's what I was looking for.
So what was I looking for?
A phone sandwich?
I don't care what it is.
Not that one?
What?
You just did a beautiful backwards voice.
Is that it?
The skewer.
It was a skewer.
Maybe.
You know what I'm sure everyone watching this is thinking?
The way he opened the kaname... so polite.
Polite?
Like your umbrellas.
Chitter, chitter, chitter!
Ushira!
Oh, my God.
That's great!
Oh, no!
A scalp care brush!
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you so much.
It really helps keep my hair in place.
This is so tight.
Now Kaname won't look so shaggy.
It's so shaggy.
I wish you'd use it.
I wanna see it now.
Woooow!
It's about time.
It's time! It's about time!
Cardboard cardboard cardboard cardboard
Well, thank you very much, I'm really happy!
Yay!
Congratulations!
So, it's me and you now.
Why don't we go with two, just the two of us?
We'll see which one you like better.
I just want to talk about which one I like better.
I don't care either way.
I'll go this way.
Which way do you want to go? I think I'll go this way.
Is this okay? Captain Sumo.
All right.
Yes, it's decided!
Well, in terms of the size of the bag...
I've decided.
One of us will get the incense.
The biggest one is this one.
One of them is a stand.
Okay, let's open it!
Which one do you want to open first?
I'll open it.
Size-wise, yeah.
I'll put it right there.
That's it.
Ehhhhhh!
What was in here?
The size of this bag.
This?
Oh, my gosh!
This is the incense.
Stylish!
Fashionable, what?
Is this what incense is?
There are a lot of long ones, but this one is really short.
It's really short, so you can just put it on a tiny plate.
You just put it on a little plate and it smells
just by putting it on a tiny plate.
It's a good size.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's not here.
What are you doing?
Here it is again, like this.
But it's okay. It's okay. I'll put it up all over the place.
That's because it's dangerous.
I'm just a fireman.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you very much.
So that means...
Oh!
That's a nice grill.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa!
Uh, over here.
It's a phone stand!
So cute!
Where do you want it?
Not a stuffed animal?
It's a phone stand.
How does it work?
I don't know how.
Maybe you can stand it right here, like this.
Put it on this leg.
That's what he said.
You put your phone right here, like this.
Wow! Hey, you know what?
That picture frame.
Can I put it here?
Yes, it's nice.
A picture frame?
It's cute!
That's what I'm talking about.
No, it's the other way around! Santa's gonna get blood on his hands and in his head.
That's right.
He's so sharp.
Here. You can take it home with you, sir.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
So, um...
I'll take it.
Oh, I'm so happy! This is so cool!
It looks great on you!
I love it!
I think it was fate!
I'm going to sleep with Wataru!
Great!
Please put your phone up!
The good thing about this is that it's that really
First of all, it looks like a stuffed animal
and the cute face.
And the fact that it's a phone stand is a rarity!
That's why I chose it.
It's great! I'm so glad I chose it.
I'm so glad I chose this one.
This is the phone stand!
And that's it!
It was a special Christmas gift exchange!
Cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu.
Watch this video and have a very happy Christmas!
I hope you have a very happy Christmas!
That's all for now, the trick is on me!
Thank you very much!
Merry Christmas!
See you next year!